testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Hello. No as soon as I turned this on
this arrived so today's late-night snack is
tada. I was going to eat squid but
Yoajeong caught my eye guys. Hmm.
So I'm going to eat Yoajeong.
Uh why does my face look so bad today?
Anyway should I show you my Yoajeong pick?
I love tangerines so much that it's only tangerines. Just tangerines and chocolate.
Actually it's true I ordered Yoajeong because I wanted to eat tangerines. Because Yoajeong's
tangerines are good. Not tangerines oranges.
So sour.
I got inspired by Kwangsoo sunbaenim so I should do Bubble
diligently.
What can I do better than Kwangsoo sunbaenim? Oh I
can do livestreams so I decided to turn on a livestream. Guys
are you asking if I'm tired? I'm not tired. I always eat at this time
after festivals. So usually at this time I just
watch dramas or watch shows like Epicase or
Pinggyego while eating so I'm not really tired.
You're asking about Hanyang? Today's festival was really fun. Hanyang University
you know what? When we went to Hanyang University it was probably last year. Around this time back then
it poured not just regular rain but a heavy downpour so at Hanyang
it was a bit of a shame but also really fun
somehow. I felt a bit sorry because we couldn't show our performance properly
and our condition didn't seem great but
on the other hand if we just got hit by a little bit of rain
we'd be worried about what to do and if our makeup is okay
but since it was pouring we just let go and performed so happily
I remember that. Who else would get to dance
in a pouring rain like that. Honestly that kind of experience is priceless.
Honestly just standing in the pouring rain without an umbrella as an adult
is a rare experience so just going through that
was such a huge experience for us. I was so happy then
but today the weather was so good. Unlike last year. So I felt
so good that I kinda wished it poured again.
Because last year's Hanyang University festival was so much fun.
The hanbok looks good on me? Thanks. That's a relief.
For the hanbok I actually debated whether to do a half-updo or leave my hair down
but
my hair stylist suggested keeping it neat in one
style since it's a hanbok. They said it would look good so we
went with this hairstyle and I really like it too. But why
do the comments keep stopping?
Why is this happening right? I'm not the only one seeing the comments stop right? Why
does it keep stopping? Then I have to try harder.
Kwangsoo sunbaenim is doing Bubble so diligently right now so we should try harder
together. Well
uh
looking at it ah it's doing it again again again
buffering
Why is it like this? It's driving me crazy. Is it usually like this. It wasn't this bad
before so why is it doing this?
Why am I speaking formally? Why do you hate it when I speak formally?
I'm just a bit shy. It's been a while since we saw each other.
Today's makeup is red. Red.
I love cosmetics this much and I've gotten other ads but you know how sad it is
that I don't get cosmetic ads?
I'm a total makeup geek. I'm a real makeup geek. I still haven't gotten
any cosmetic ads. So guys
any brand is welcome.
Now
this is Alternative Stereo
this one
I bought this for my mom and she really loved it.
But my makeup today was mostly done by
my stylist so I don't know what brands they are.
Makeup holy grail. My makeup holy grail is ah my
makeup tip is hmm.
I draw my aegyosal shadow where it sits when I smile.
Because I have two aegyosal positions
I think I mentioned this before
when I smile it's slightly up here oh when I don't smile it's up here and when I smile
it's down here. It gets indented right here like this.
But since I
am always smiling if I draw it where my aegyosal is when I'm expressionless
how should I say this? It makes my eyes look smaller?
If I do that I'm always smiling. I keep smiling like this but it's drawn up here
so if I draw the aegyosal there it's worse than not drawing it at all
and I realized that.
It looks awkward if I don't smile. Right right. It looks awkward if I don't smile guys. So
what should I call it? I only draw it like this for performances. On stage
I'm constantly smiling so I only draw it like this for performances and normally
I draw it right in the middle of when I smile and when I don't but there isn't a huge
difference anyway so
people were saying my midface suddenly looked shorter? Since this
promotion some people said my midface got shorter and that's all thanks
to this aegyosal.
Ah this is seriously so good.
Flover have you ever yelled when you were angry?
Ah I've never yelled out of anger before.
When I get really mad how should I put it? When I get too
mad. Hmm.
Hmm. When my anger reaches its peak I just
shut down completely.
And I cry. I just cry. I really want to fix this. I really
badly want to fix it.
What should I do about this? I don't want to look overly emotional
but I get so mad that I just cry
The last time I got mad
Well I rarely have reasons to be mad. What's there to be mad about? Are there things
to be mad about?
When I recently fought with my mom and dad
I did get a bit mad then. I'll handle it myself.
Ah stop worrying about it. Something like that
I went to my parents' house and my mom kept
nagging me. So I was like alright I got it. Ah
okay okay. Yeah. I get it. Ah I said I got it.
When I reply like that my mom goes hey Baek Jiheon
is that how I raised you? It turns into that. Then I go
no
I told you to stop. It turns into this. Then
my mom goes hey where did you learn to be so disrespectful? To an adult. Huh
I didn't raise you like that. She says that. Then I'm like
ah then you should have stopped. Mom I'm also getting ah you should stop. Mom why
why do you keep saying the same thing over and over? I'm having a hard time too. Mom. Like
that. Then my dad next to her comes in and that's scary. When my dad
steps in it's all over. If my dad goes hey Baek Jiheon
I just say okay and immediately go straight to my room. I have to go straight to my room
right away. It's so scary. My dad getting mad is the scariest thing.
Because my dad rarely ever gets mad.
But when I fight with my mom he always takes her side and that makes me so sad.
Then I just start crying.
When my dad gets mad like that I just end up crying.
Like seriously I have no one on my side. Things like that
The chat isn't going up. It keeps stopping one by one now.
I almost raised my hand just now
to hit it
Hell's Kitchen
I should go watch it. I want to go watch it but I keep having
festivals at that time so I don't have time to go watch it.
I really want to go too.
I can't read the comments anymore. If it's like this I can't read them.
Will restarting it fix it? I highly doubt it. What should I do?
Should I try restarting it? Okay.